{
  "org": [
    "PREPS"
  ],
  "Admins": [
    {
      "firstName": "kingdom",
      "lastName": "adele",
      "adminusername": "kingdomadele",
      "level": 10,
      "myExams": [],
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "Exams": [
    {
      "adminusername": "kingdomadele",
      "exam": "quiz",
      "duration": "10",
      "Questions": "5",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "adminusername": "kingdomadele",
      "exam": "python3",
      "duration": "10",
      "Questions": "10",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "adminusername": "kingdomadele",
      "exam": "node js",
      "duration": "10",
      "Questions": "5",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "adminusername": "kingdomadele",
      "exam": "",
      "duration": "",
      "Questions": "",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "StudentsRecords": [
    {
      "firstName": "kingdom",
      "lastName": "adele",
      "username": "kingdomadele",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 5,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "1",
      "myExamName": "quiz",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "quiz",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 5,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "firstName": "kingsley",
      "lastName": "ike",
      "username": "kingsleyike",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 5,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "1",
      "myExamName": "quiz",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "quiz",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 5,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "adel",
      "username": "kingadel",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 5,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 5,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "ben",
      "username": "kingben",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 5,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 5,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "green",
      "username": "kinggreen",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 5,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "1",
      "myExamName": "quiz",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "quiz",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 5,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "firstName": "kingsley",
      "lastName": "adel",
      "username": "kingsleyadel",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 5,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 5,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "han",
      "username": "kinghan",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 5,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 5,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "man",
      "username": "kingman",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 4,
      "wrong": 1,
      "score": 80,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 80,
          "correct": 4,
          "wrong": 1
        }
      ],
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "code",
      "username": "kingcode",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 5,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 5,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "ade",
      "username": "kingade",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 10,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 10,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "name",
      "username": "kingname",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 10,
      "wrong": 0,
      "score": 100,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 100,
          "correct": 10,
          "wrong": 0
        }
      ],
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "firstName": "king",
      "lastName": "go",
      "username": "kinggo",
      "isdone": "yes",
      "correct": 9,
      "wrong": 1,
      "score": 90,
      "myExamId": "2",
      "myExamName": "python3",
      "Result": [
        {
          "myExamName": "python3",
          "score": 90,
          "correct": 9,
          "wrong": 1
        }
      ],
      "id": 12
    }
  ],
  "exam1": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements about fixed mindset is true?",
      "option1": "When adopting a fixed mindset, you are more likely to use the word “yet” when you talk about what you can’t do, or what you don’t know.",
      "option2": "Students who adopted a fixed mindset were more likely to see their failures as indicators that they were not smart, rather than as opportunities to learn.",
      "option3": "If someone is adopting a fixed mindset, their beliefs about the nature of intelligence are more accurate than someone adopting a growth mindset.",
      "option4": "Students who were trained to have a fixed mindset performed better in mathematics than students who were trained to have a growth mindset.",
      "Correctanswer": "Students who adopted a fixed mindset were more likely to see their failures as indicators that they were not smart, rather than as opportunities to learn.",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which factor was the highest predictor of success for Spelling Bee (spelling competition) contestants?",
      "option1": "IQ",
      "option2": "Grit",
      "option3": "Social intelligence",
      "option4": "Wealth",
      "Correctanswer": "Grit",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is growth mindset?",
      "option1": "Holding a belief that one’s character, intelligence, and/or creative ability are carved in stone and can’t change in any meaningful way.",
      "option2": "Holding a belief that success is a result of one’s innate intelligence and/or talents.",
      "option3": "Holding a belief that one’s intelligence and abilities can grow through dedication and hard work.",
      "option4": "Holding a belief that your failure means that you lack what it takes to be successful.",
      "Correctanswer": "Holding a belief that one’s intelligence and abilities can grow through dedication and hard work.",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is grit?",
      "option1": "Growth mindset",
      "option2": "Positive self-talk",
      "option3": "Fixed mindset",
      "option4": "Perseverance in the face of challenges",
      "Correctanswer": "Perseverance in the face of challenges",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a step in the Faynmen learning technique?",
      "option1": "Pretend to teach a concept you want to learn about to a student in the sixth grade.",
      "option2": "make things bigger, more complex",
      "option3": "Identify gaps in your explanation. Go back to the source material to better understand it.",
      "option4": "Organize and simplify.",
      "Correctanswer": "make things bigger, more complex",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What command would you use to list files on Linux?",
      "option1": "which",
      "option2": "pwd",
      "option3": "list",
      "option4": "ls",
      "Correctanswer": "ls",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "What does LTS stand for?",
      "option1": "Long Term Support",
      "option2": "Long Time Support",
      "option3": "Last Terrible Service",
      "option4": "Last Time Service",
      "Correctanswer": "Long Term Support",
      "id": 7
    }
  ],
  "exam2": [
    {
      "question": "What does this command line print? <div class='examx'> >>> print(\"Holberton school\") </div>",
      "option1": "Holberton",
      "option2": "‘Holberton school’",
      "option3": "“Holberton school”",
      "option4": "Holberton school",
      "Correctanswer": "Holberton school",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What does this command line print? <div class='examx'> <p> >>> a = 'Python is cool'</p> <p> >>> print(a[-2]) </p></div>",
      "option1": "ol",
      "option2": "Nothing",
      "option3": "l",
      "option4": "o",
      "Correctanswer": "o",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What does this command line print? <div class='examx'> <p>>>> a = 'Python is cool'</p><p> >>> print(a[:6])</p></div>",
      "option1": "Pytho",
      "option2": "is cool",
      "option3": "Python",
      "option4": "Python is",
      "Correctanswer": "Python",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does this command line print? <div class='examx'> <p>>>> a = 'Python is cool'</p><p>>>> print(a[7:-5])</p>  </div>",
      "option1": "is",
      "option2": "on",
      "option3": "Python",
      "option4": "nohtyP",
      "Correctanswer": "is",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Who created Python?",
      "option1": "Julien Barbier",
      "option2": "Yukihiro Matsumoto",
      "option3": "Guido van Rossum",
      "option4": "Yukihiro Barbier",
      "Correctanswer": "Guido van Rossum",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What does this command line print? <div class='examx'>>>> print(f\"{98} Battery street, {'San Francisco'}\") </div>",
      "option1": "'98 Battery street, San Francisco'",
      "option2": "San Francisco Battery street, 98",
      "option3": "8 Battery street, San",
      "option4": "98 Battery street, San Francisco",
      "Correctanswer": "98 Battery street, San Francisco",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "What does this command line print? <div class='examx'><p>>>> a = \"Python is cool\"</p><p>>>> print(a[4])</p></div>",
      "option1": "P",
      "option2": "h",
      "option3": "n",
      "option4": "o",
      "Correctanswer": "o",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "What does this command line print? <div class='examx'>>>> print(f\"{98} Battery street\") </div>",
      "option1": "98 Battery street",
      "option2": "8 Battery street",
      "option3": "f\"98 Battery street\"",
      "option4": "9 Battery street",
      "Correctanswer": "98 Battery street",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; b = a xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a[2] = 10 xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; b xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "b",
      "option2": "a",
      "option3": "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
      "option4": "[1, 2, 10, 4]",
      "Correctanswer": "[1, 2, 10, 4]",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a[-1] xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "-1",
      "option2": "[4, 3, 2, 1]",
      "option3": "2",
      "option4": "4",
      "Correctanswer": "4",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a[2] = 10 xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
      "option2": "[1, 2, 10, 10]",
      "option3": "[1, 10, 3, 4]",
      "option4": "[1, 2, 10, 4]",
      "Correctanswer": "[1, 2, 10, 4]",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a[1:3] xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "[1, 2, 3]",
      "option2": "[1, 2]",
      "option3": "[2, 3]",
      "option4": "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
      "Correctanswer": "[2, 3]",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a[0] xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
      "option2": "1",
      "option3": "[1, 2]",
      "option4": "2",
      "Correctanswer": "1",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; len(a) xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "2",
      "option2": "8",
      "option3": "4",
      "option4": "6",
      "Correctanswer": "4",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a.append(5) xcpx xopx  &gt;&gt;&gt; len(a) xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "2",
      "option2": "5",
      "option3": "6",
      "option4": "4",
      "Correctanswer": "5",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a[-3] xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "-3",
      "option2": "[4, 3]",
      "option3": "2",
      "option4": "[1, 3]",
      "Correctanswer": "2",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; b = a xcpx xopx &gt;&gt;&gt; b xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
      "option2": "a",
      "option3": "[1]",
      "option4": "1",
      "Correctanswer": "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
      "id": 17,
      "EditedQuestion": {
        "question": "What do these lines print? ggg &lt;div class=&#039;examx&#039;&gt; &lt;p&gt; &gt;&gt;&gt; a = [1, 2, 3, 4] &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &gt;&gt;&gt; b = a &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &gt;&gt;&gt; b &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;",
        "option1": "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
        "option2": "a",
        "option3": "[1]",
        "option4": "1",
        "Correctanswer": "[1, 2, 3, 4]"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx if 12 == 48/4: xcpx xopx xtabx print(&quot;Holberton&quot;) xcpx xopx else: xcpx xopx xtabx print(&quot;School&quot;) xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "School",
      "option2": "Holberton",
      "option3": "Holberton School",
      "option4": "School Holberton",
      "Correctanswer": "Holberton",
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx xopx for i in range(4): xcpx xopx xtabx print(i, end=&quot; &quot;) xcpx xcdivx",
      "option1": "1 2 3 4",
      "option2": "0 1 2 3 4",
      "option3": "1 2 3",
      "option4": "0 1 2 3",
      "Correctanswer": "0 1 2 3",
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx a = 12 xbrx if a &lt; 2: xbrx xtabx print(&quot;Holberton&quot;) xbrx elif a % 2 == 0: xbrx xtabx print(&quot;C is fun&quot;) xbrx else: xbrx xtabx print(&quot;School&quot;)",
      "option1": "Holberton",
      "option2": "C is fun",
      "option3": "School",
      "option4": "Holbert",
      "Correctanswer": "C is fun",
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx for i in range(2, 10, 2): xbrx xtabx print(i, end=&quot; &quot;)",
      "option1": "2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10",
      "option2": "2 4 6 8",
      "option3": "2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9",
      "option4": "4 6 8 10 12 14 16 18",
      "Correctanswer": "2 4 6 8",
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx if True: xbrx xtabx print(&quot;Holberton&quot;) xbrx else: xbrx xtabx print(&quot;School&quot;)",
      "option1": "School",
      "option2": "Holberton",
      "option3": "Holbert",
      "option4": "Holberton School",
      "Correctanswer": "Holberton",
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx a = 12 xbrx if a &gt; 2: xbrx xtabx if a % 2 == 0: xbrx xtabx xtabx print(&quot;Holberton&quot;) xbrx xtabx else: xbrx xtabx xtabx print(&quot;C is fun&quot;) xbrx else: xbrx print(&quot;School&quot;)",
      "option1": "Holberton",
      "option2": "C is fun",
      "option3": "School",
      "option4": "Holberton School",
      "Correctanswer": "Holberton",
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx if 12 == 48/4 and False: xbrx xtabx print(&quot;Holberton&quot;) xbrx else: xbrx xtabx print(&quot;School&quot;)",
      "option1": "School",
      "option2": "Holberton",
      "option3": "Holbert",
      "option4": "Holberton School",
      "Correctanswer": "School",
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "What do these lines print? xodivx for i in range(2, 4): xbrx xtabx print(i, end=&quot; &quot;)",
      "option1": "2 4",
      "option2": "3 4",
      "option3": "2 3",
      "option4": "2 3 4",
      "Correctanswer": "2 3",
      "id": 25
    }
  ],
  "exam3": [],
  "exam4": [],
  "exam5": [],
  "exam6": [],
  "exam7": [],
  "exam8": [],
  "exam9": [],
  "exam10": [],
  "exam11": [],
  "exam12": [],
  "exam13": [],
  "exam14": [],
  "exam15": [],
  "exam16": [],
  "exam17": [],
  "exam18": [],
  "exam19": [],
  "exam20": [],
  "exam21": [],
  "exam22": [],
  "exam23": [],
  "exam24": [],
  "exam25": [],
  "exam26": [],
  "exam27": [],
  "exam28": [],
  "exam29": [],
  "exam30": [],
  "exam31": [],
  "exam32": [],
  "exam33": [],
  "exam34": [],
  "exam35": [],
  "exam36": [],
  "exam37": [],
  "exam38": [],
  "exam39": [],
  "exam40": [],
  "exam41": [],
  "exam42": [],
  "exam43": [],
  "exam44": [],
  "exam45": [],
  "exam46": [],
  "exam47": [],
  "exam48": [],
  "exam49": [],
  "exam50": []
}